<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>David Araújo</title>
    <link>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on David Araújo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 15:51:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Everything Is A File</title>
      <link>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/posts/02-everything-is-a-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 15:51:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/posts/02-everything-is-a-file/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents What is a file? Is my red blue for you, or my green your green, too? What types of files are there? Why should I care? What is a file? Link to heading Files, everything is a file! You may have heard this phrase in relation to Linux. It’s quite popular among Linux enthusiasts, but beyond being a catchy sentence, what does it actually mean?
To understand this, we first need to define what a file is at its core.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safety Glasses First</title>
      <link>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/posts/01-safety-glasses-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 11:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/posts/01-safety-glasses-first/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Strong roots Vitualization is the name of the game Touch it with a stick Clean up and bleach Have Fun! I&amp;rsquo;m paranoid about safety.
As much as I love getting my hands on that new, shiny, (un)known malicious application or scratching that itch of clicking on those sketchy phishing emails I tell myself only idiots click on, the one thing I love more is knowing that after I get bored doing it, my machine will not be infected and that little voice in my head won&amp;rsquo;t be telling me that I need to, again, nuke my disk and re-install my OS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/posts/00-hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 21:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/posts/00-hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Here we go&amp;hellip;
If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, it&amp;rsquo;s probably because you either follow me closely (which is a bit concerning), stumbled upon it randomly (what were you even searching for?), or I did something so incredible that you think everything I write is pure gold and MUST be read. Well, if that&amp;rsquo;s the case, let me burst your bubble: this post isn&amp;rsquo;t anything special.
Honestly, I don&amp;rsquo;t know why I&amp;rsquo;m starting this blog or if this will be the first and last post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 23:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been passionate about technology since I was young and am now pursuing a Master’s in Cybersecurity at the University of Aveiro. My main interests are in software development, network security, and malware analysis.
My research started with Software Defined Networks during a Graduate Research Scholarship. Currently, I’m working on improving authentication and authorization for legacy non-5G devices in 5G networks.
When I’m not working, I’m either brainstorming new projects, firefighting, or trail running—always staying focused and ready for the next challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
