<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tools on David Araújo</title>
    <link>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/tags/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tools on David Araújo</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:17:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/tags/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Homeless Self Hosting</title>
      <link>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/posts/06-homeless-self-hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/posts/06-homeless-self-hosting/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents As specific as it is simple I needed a coach All hail Apps Script The Architecture: No Server, No Problem The &amp;lsquo;Secret Sauce&amp;rsquo;: Gemini 2.5 Pro Conclusion: The Environment is the Message Project page Like usual, you can find all documents and code here Has specific as it is simple Link to heading In this cookie-cutter world, we have managed to make ourselves fit in whatever shape fits the majority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old But Gold</title>
      <link>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/posts/05-old-but-gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 12:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/posts/05-old-but-gold/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Amazing is simple Simple isn&amp;rsquo;t basic Limitations On the shoulders of giants Quick and easy Project page Like usual, you can find all documents and code here So, before continuing, I must tell you the context of this post. I recently finished college (hurray for me!) and I started working for Cognizant doing Android Reverse Engineering for Google. Due to that, I got a whole new appreciation for what we&amp;rsquo;ll be discussing today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety Glasses First</title>
      <link>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/posts/01-safety-glasses-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 11:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidjosearaujo.github.io/posts/01-safety-glasses-first/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Strong roots Vitualization is the name of the game Touch it with a stick Clean up and bleach Have Fun! I&amp;rsquo;m paranoid about safety.&#xA;As much as I love getting my hands on that new, shiny, (un)known malicious application or scratching that itch of clicking on those sketchy phishing emails I tell myself only idiots click on, the one thing I love more is knowing that after I get bored doing it, my machine will not be infected and that little voice in my head won&amp;rsquo;t be telling me that I need to, again, nuke my disk and re-install my OS.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
